Inventory of the Mimi Benzell papers, 1897-1972 (bulk 1930-1972)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Printed Music, Loose Sheets:
  - VOODOO SPIRITS, lyrics by Della Hayward, music by Frank La Forge, undated (Box 33)
  - WAIT TILL YOU SEE HER, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - WAKE WITH THE DAWN, Ruggiero Leoneavallo, undated (Box 33)
  - WALKING HAPPY, lyrics by Sammy Cahn, music by James Van Heuser, undated (Box 33)
  - A WALK IN THE COUNTRY, by Bart Howard, undated (Box 33)
  - WALK THE PATH OF PEACE, words by Atra Baer, music by Martin Kalmanoff, undated (Box 33)
  - WALK-UP, by Bart Howard, undated (Box 33)
  - WALTER'S PRIZE SONG, by Richard Wagner, undated (Box 33)
  - WALTZ AT MAXIM'S, words by Alan Jay Lerner, music by Frederick Loewe, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - WASHINGTON SQUARE DANCE, words and music by Irving Berlin, undated (Box 33)
  - WAS IT A DREAM, lyrics and music by Sam Coslow, Larry Spier, and Addy Britt, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WATER MILL, music by R. Vaughan Williams, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WAY IT USED TO BE, music by Franco Cassano and Corrado Conti, English lyrics by Roger Cook and Roder Greenaway, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WAY YOU LOOK TO-NIGHT, music by Jerome Kern, lyrics by Dorothy Fields, undated (Box 33)
  - WE CAN LIVE ON LOVE, lyrics by Al Dubin, music by Jimmy McHugh, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WEDDING CAKE-WALK, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WEDDING SAMBA, by Abraham Ellstein, Allan Small, and Joseph Liebowitz, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WEE BUTTERFLY, by Mana-Zucca, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WEEKEND OF A PRIVATE SECRETARY, lyrics by Johnny Mercer, music by Bernie Hanighen, undated (Box 33)
  - WE HAVE TO LEAVE, lyrics by Sammy Cahn, music by Jule Styne, undated (Box 33)
  - WE'LL MEET AGAIN, words and music by Ross Parker and Hughie Charles, undated (Box 33)
  - WE'LL NEVER KNOW, by Irving Berlin, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - WE SPEAK OF YOU OFTEN, lyrics by Dedette Lee Hill, music by Johnny Marks, undated (Box 33)
  - WESTWIND, words by Ogdan Nash, music by Kurt Weill, undated (Box 33)
  - WE THREE, words and music by Dick Dobertson, Nelson Cogane, and Sammy Mysels, undated (Box 33)
  - WE'VE COME A LONG WAY TOGETHER, lyrics by Ted Koehler, music by Sammy H. Stept, undated (Box 33)
  - WHAT A MAN, words and music by Leslie Bricusse and Anthony Newley, undated (Box 33)
  - WHAT HAVE YOU DONE ALL DAY?, music by Richard Hardt, undated (Box 33)
  - WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THAT GETS ME, words and music by Leo Robin and Ralph Rainger, undated (Box 33)
  - WHAT IS THIS THING CALLED LOVE, by Cole Porter, undated (Box 33)
  - WHAT MAKES THE SUNSET?, lyrics by Sammy Cahn, music by Jule Styne, undated (Box 33)
  - WHAT'S IN THE AIR TO-DAY?, words and music by Robert Eden, undated (Box 33)
  - WHAT'S THE USE OF WOND'RIN', music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, undated (Box 33)
  - WHAT WILL I TELL MY HEART, words and music by Peter Tinturin and Jack Lawrence, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN I BRING TO YOU COLOUR'D TOYS, music by John Alden Carpenter, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN I DANCE WITH THE PERSON I LOVE, music by Mark Sandrich Jr., lyrics by Sidney Michaels, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN I FALL IN LOVE, music by Victor Young, lyrics by Edward Heyman, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN I GO ON THE STAGE, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN I GROW TOO OLD TO DREAM, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Sigmund Romberg, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN I LOST YOU, by Irving Berlin, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN LOVE COMES YOUR WAY, music and lyrics by Cole Porter, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN LOVE IS KIND, arranged by A. L., undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN THAT MAN IS DEAD AND GONE, by Irving Berlin, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN THE IDLE POOR BECOME THE IDLE RICH, lyrics by E. Y. Harburg, music by Burton Lane, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN THE WEATHER'S BETTER, music by Jule Styne, lyrics by Betty Comden, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN YOU'RE A LONG, LONG WAY FROM HOME, music by Sam M. Lewis, music by George W. Meyer, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN YOU'RE AWAY, lyrics by Henry M. Blossom, music by Victor Herbert, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN YOU WALK IN THE ROOM, lyrics by Dorothy Fields, music by Sigmund Romberg, undated (Box 33)
  - WHEN YOU WISH UPON A STAR, lyrics by Ned Washington, music by Leigh Harline, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - WHERE CAN SHE BE?, words by Burton Shevelove, music by Perry Lafferty, undated (Box 33)
  - WHERE IS PEACE?, words and music by Oscar Kramer, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - WHERE WOULD YOU BE WITHOUT ME?, words and music by Leslie Bricusse and Anthony Newley, undated (Box 33)
  - WHERE YOU ARE, words by Laurel Wallace, music by Charles Huerter, undated (Box 33)
  - WHILE THE CITY SLEEPS, lyrics by Lee Adams, music by Charles Strouse, undated (Box 33)
  - WHISPERING HOPE, words and music by Alice Hawthorne, undated (Box 33)
  - WHISPERING IN THE DARK, words and music by Leo Robin and Frederick Hollander, undated (Box 33)
  - WHITE BIRDS, by Mana-Zucca, undated (Box 33)
  - WHITE SAILS, by Nick Kenny, Charles Kenny, Harry Archer, undated (Box 33)
  - WHITHER RUNNETH MY SWEETHEART?, arranged by Estelle Liebling, undated (Box 33)
  - WHO?, book by Otto Harbach and Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Jerome Kern, undated (Box 33)
  - WHO AM I?, lyrics by Walter Bullock, music by Jule Styne, undated (Box 33)
  - WHO BELONGS TO THAT SMILE?, lyrics and music by Will Lorin, undated (Box 33)
  - WHO CAN I TURN TO, words and music by Leslie Bricusse and Anthony Newley, undated (Box 33)
  - WHO KNOWS, words and music by J. Bruce Orcutt, undated (Box 33)
  - WHO KNOWS?, words by Eddie Mathews, music by Dcik Vinson, undated (Box 33)
  - WHO KNOWS?, words and music by Cole Porter, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WHOLE WORLD KNOWS, by Fritz Kreisler, undated (Box 33)
  - WHO WANTS TO FALL IN LOVE, by Bart Howard, undated (Box 33)
  - WHO, WHO, WHO, WHO, words and music by Don Nickey, undated (Box 33)
  - WHY CAN'T IT BE YOU?, words by Ruth Webb, music by Phyllis Webb, undated (Box 33)
  - WHY CRY BABY?, lyrics by Bill Hampton, music by George Duning, undated (Box 33)
  - WHY DID WE EVER SAY GOOD-BYE?, words and music by Bill Lennerts, undated (Box 33)
  - WHY DO I LOVE YOU?, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Jerome Kern, undated (Box 33)
  - WHY DO THE WRONG PEOPLE TRAVEL?, words and music by Cole Porter, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - WHY SHOULD I CARE?, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 33)
  - WHY SO PALE AND WAN, FOND LOVER?, by Norman Dell Joio, undated (Box 33)
  - WIEGENLIED, Johannes Brahms, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WILD FLOWER'S SONG, by Paul Hindenith, undated (Box 33)
  - WILLOW SONG, music by Douglas Moore, lyrics by John Latouche, undated (Box 33)
  - WILL O' THE WISP, words by Torrence Benjamin, music by Charles Gilbert Spross, undated (Box 33)
  - WILL YOU REMEMBER, lyrics by Alda Johnson Young, music by Sigmund Romberg, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WIND SINGS WELCOME, by Elinor Remick Warren, undated (Box 33)
  - WISHING, words and music by B.G. De Sylva, undated (Box 33)
  - WISH YOU WERE HERE, music and lyrics by Harold Rome, undated (Box 33)
  - WITH A SMILE AND A SONG, words by Larry Morey, music by Frank Churchill, undated (Box 33)
  - WITH A SONG IN MY HEART, words by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 33)
  - WITH MY SHILLELAGH UNDER MY ARM, words and music by Billy O'Brien and Raymond Wallace, undated (Box 33)
  - WITH THE WIND AND THE RAIN IN YOUR HAIR, words and music by Jack Lawrence and Clara Edwards, undated (Box 33)
  - WOMAN IS A RASCAL, music by Baldwin Bergersen, lyrics by William Archibald, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WONDER OF YOU, lyrics by Arthur Herzog, Jr., music by Eduardo S. de Fuentes, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WOODEN SOLDIER AND THE CHINA DOLL, lyrics by Charles Newman, music by Isham Jones, undated (Box 33)
  - A WOMAN IS A SOMETIME THING, music by George Gershwin, lyrics by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WORLD IS IN MY ARMS, words by E. Y. Harburg, music by Burton Lane, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WORLD IS MINE, lyrics by Holt Marvell, music by George Posford, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WORLD IS WAITING FOR THE SUNRISE, words by Eugene Lockhart, music by Ernest Seitz, undated (Box 33)
  - THE WORLD IS YOUR BALLOON, words by E. Y. Harburg, music by Sammy Fain, undated (Box 33)
  - WOULD YOU, lyrics by Arthur Freed, music by Nacio Herb Brown, undated (Box 33)
  - THE YAM, by Irving Berlin, undated (Box 33)
  - YESTERDAYS, words by Otto Harbach, music by Jerome Kern, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - A YIDDISHE MOMME, lyrics by Jack Yellen, music by Jack Yellen and Lew Pollack, undated (Box 33)
  - THE YODEL WALTZ, words by D.S. Noble, music by Harry Noble, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU, lyrics by Mack Gordon, music by Josef Myrow, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU AND I, lyrics by Howard Dietz, music by Johann Strauss, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU AND THE NIGHT AND THE MUSIC, words by Howard Dietz, music by Arthur Schwartz, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU ARE FREE, words by William Le Baron, music by Victor Jacobi, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU ARE LOVE, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Jerome Kern, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU CAME A LONG WAY FROM ST. LOUIS, lyrics by Bob Russell, music by John Benson Brooks, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU CAN DO NO WRONG, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU CAN LIVE WITH A BROKEN HEART, lyrics by Al Lewis music by Marvin Kahn and Arthur Burman, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU’D BE SO NICE TO COME HOME TO, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH YOU CAN SUFFER, words and music by Cliff Friend and Dave Franklin, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU DON'T KNOW PAREE, lyrics and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU GO TO MY HEAD, lyrics by Haven Gillespie, music by J. Fred Coots, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU GROW SWEETER AS THE YEARS GO BY, words and music by Johnny Mercer, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU HAVE MY HEART, words by Mort Goodman, music by Lillian Rosedale Goodman, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU KISSED ME, lyrics by Dorothy Fields, music by Morton Gould, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU LEAVE ME BREATHLESS, words by Ralph Freed, music by Frederick Hollander, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU'LL BE REMINDED OF ME, words and music by George Jessel, Jack Meskill and Ted Shapiro, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU'LL NEVER WALK ALONE, music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU MAKE ME FEEL SO YOUNG, lyrics by Mack Gordon, music by Josef Myrow, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU MEET THE NICEST PEOPLE IN YOUR DREAMS, words and music by Al Hoffman, Al Goodhart, and Manny Kurtz, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU MUST HAVE BEEN A BEAUTIFUL BABY, lyrics by Johnny Mercer, music by Harry Warren, undated (Box 33)
  - YOUNG AND WARM AND WONDERFUL, words by Hy Zaret, music by Lou Singer, undated (Box 33)
  - YOUNGER THAN SPRINGTIME, words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU'RE A SWEET LITTLE HEADACHE, words and music by Leo Robin and Ralph Rainger, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU'RE DANGEROUS, words by Johnny Burke, music by Jimmy Van Heusen, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU'RE DEVASTATING, words by Otto Harbach, music by Jerone Kern, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU'RE DOIN' ALL RIGHT, lyrics by Mack Gordon, music by Josef Myrow, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU'RE JUST IN LOVE, lyrics and music by Irving Berlin, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - YOUR EYES SHINE IN MY OWN, musical adaptation and lyrics by Ann Ronell, undated (Box 33)
  - YOUR LIPS ARE LIKE CHAMPAGE, lyrics by Jimmy Eaton, music by Robert Stolz, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU'RE MY DISH, lyrics by Harold Adamson, music by Jimmy McHugh, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU'RE NOT IN MY ARMS TONIGHT, words by Ned Washington, music by Victor Young, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU'RE SO DESIRABLE, words and music by Ray Noble, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU'RE THE ONLY STAR, by Gene Autry, undated (Box 33)
  - YOURS, lyrics by Jack Sherr, music by Gonzalo Roig, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU SAY THE SWEETEST THINGS, lyrics by Mack Gordon, music by Harry Warren, undated (Box 33)
  - YOURS FOR A SONG, words by Billy Rose and Ted Fetter, music by Dana Suesse, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU SHALL HAVE YOUR RED ROSE, music by Rhea Silberta, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU THINK OF EV'RYTHING, lyrics by Joseph McCarthy and Billy Rose, music by Jimmy Van Heusen, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU WALKED OUT OF THE PICTURE, by Little Jack Little, Dave Oppenheim and Henry Tobias, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU WILL WEAT VELVET, words by Douglass Cross, music by George Cory, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU WONDERFUL YOU, lyrics by Jack Brooks and Saul Chaplin, music by Harry Warren, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - YOU WON'T BELIEVE ME, lyrics by Harry Conley, music by Jack Hendersen and George Kilroy, undated (Box 33)
  - A ZEMER, words by Aaron Peitlan, music by Samuel Rugatch, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - ZIGUENER, by Noel Coward, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - ZOL NOCH SEIN SHABOS, words by H. Roisenblatt, music by Sholom Secunda, 2 copies, undated (Box 33)
  - YEAR AFTER YEAR, by Bart Howard, undated (Box 33)
- Programs:
  - ABRAHAM LINCOLN HIGH SCHOOL SILVER ANNIVERSARY LUNCHEON, 06/18/1955 (Box 25)
  - THE AIRCRAFT AND ENGINE MANUFACTURERS OF THE UNITED STATES DINNER DANCE IN HONOR OF THE INTERNATIONAL AIR TRANSPORT ASSOCIATION, 10/20/1955 (Box 25)
  - ALFRED E. SMITH MEMORIAL DINNER, 2 copies, with 2 copies with seating arrangements, 10/18/1951 (Box 25)
  - AMERICAN HEART FUND 1953 INAUGURAL HEART DINNER, 2 copies with seating arrangements, 01/09/1953 (Box 25)
  - AMERICAN ROYAL CORONATION PAGEANT AND BALL, 1954 (Box 25)
  - THE AMERICAN THEATRE WING CANDLELIGHT EVENING, 09/19/1950 (Box 25)
  - CHICAGO DRUG AND CHEMICAL ASSOCIATION ANNUAL SPRING PARTY, 05/21/1955 (Box 25)
  - THE CONGRESSIONAL CLUB ANNUAL BREAKFAST, 05/05/1955 (Box 25)
  - EAST RIVER SAVINGS BANK ONE HUNDREDTH BIRTHDAY CELEBRATION, 05/20/1948 (Box 25)
  - FIESTA SEVILLE, 2 copies, 12/09/1951 (Box 25)
  - FOR FRED F. FLORENCE DINNER, 2 copies, 02/14/1956 (Box 25)
  - FRIARS CLUB, 2 copies, 11/09/1952 (Box 25)
  - THE GEORGE "JUNIOR" REPUBLIC, FOREIGN COMMERCE CLUB OF NEW YORK MOONLIGHT CRUISE, 2 copies, 06/27/1952 (Box 25)
  - GROCERY MANUFACTURERS OF AMERICA, INC. FORTY-SIXTH ANNUAL MEETING, BANQUET AND DANCE, 11/10/1954 (Box 25)
  - GOODYEAR A.T.A., INC. OFFICIAL LUNCHEON, 10/27/1954 (Box 25)
  - JUNIOR LEAGUE CHARITY BALL, 3 copies, 02/03/1956 (Box 25)
  - LAKE PLACID ANNUAL CROWNING OF THE KING AND QUEEN OF WINTER, 1947 (Box 25)
  - THE LAMBS PUBLIC GAMBOL, 04/22/1950 (Box 25)
  - MGM MUSICAL COMEDY THEATRE, undated (Box 25)
  - THE MUSICAL THEATER SUMMER PROGRAM, undated (Box 25)
  - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF RETAIL CLOTHIERS AND FURNISHERS ANNUAL BANQUET, 02/21/1956 (Box 25)
  - NCR GOLDEN JUBILEE OF CPC, 1954 (Box 25)
  - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF RETAIL CLOTHIERS AND FURNISHERS ANNUAL BANQUET, 10/31/1955 (Box 25)
  - PAGE ONE BALL, 1951 (Box 25)
  - THE PHILADELPHIA WOMEN'S DIVISION STATE OF ISRAEL BONDS LUNCHEON CONCERT, 3 copies, 12/16/1954 (Box 25)
  - PIERRE HOTEL, COTILLION ROOM, 2 copies, 1950 (Box 25)
  - THE POST-STANDARD SEVENTH SEMI-ANNUAL SPRING FASHION SHOW, 4 copies, 02/17/1954 (Box 25)
  - QUEENS MUSIC FESTIVAL, 3 copies, 06/15/1952 (Box 25)
  - "ROSALIE", starring Mimi Benzell, attachments, undated (Box 25)
  - ROTARY INTERNATIONAL GOLDEN ANNIVERSARY, 05/25/1955 (Box 25)
  - THE SACRED HEART HOSPITAL ASSOCIATES PRESENT MIMI BENZELL, 2 copies, 10/30/1955 (Box 25)
  - SUMMER SESSION ACTIVITIES OF IOWA STATE COLLEGE PRESENTS MIMI BENZELL, 07/07/1948 (Box 25)
  - TOURNAMENT OF ORATORS TENTH ANNIVERSARY, 2 copies, 05/05/1952 (Box 25)
  - TOWN OF PELHAM, NEW YORK TERCENTENNIAL, 10/09/1954-10/17/1954 (Box 25)
  - TRIENNIAL CONVENTION OF B'NAI B'RITH SUPREME LODGE, 03/18/1950-03/22/1950 (Box 25)
  - THE UNITED NATIONS CLUB SEVENTH ANNIVERSARY BALL AND THE UNITED NATIONS PAGEANT, 4 copies, 12/03/1948 (Box 25)
  - U.S. BREWERS FOUNDATION BANQUET, 01/19/1956 (Box 25)
  - WESTCHESTER COUNTRY CLUB ANNIVERSARY BALL, 07/23/1955 (Box 25)
  - WILLIAMSBURG SETTLEMENT, INC. ANNUAL GOLD METAL AWARD DINNER TO HON. THOMAS E. DEWEY, 2 pieces, 05/18/1952 (Box 25)
- Playbills:
  - BY THE BEAUTIFUL SEA, Music Theater, Highland Park, Illinois, 6 copies, undated (Box 25)
  - A NIGHT ON THE TOWN, Motel Pierre, 14 copies, undated (Box 25)
  - A NIGHT ON THE TOWN, Ramstein Base Theater, 8 copies, 06/22/1956 (Box 25)
  - SHOW BOAT, Music Theater, Highland Park, Illinois, 4 copies, undated (Box 25)
- Proofs:
  - 59 8x10 inch proofs of Mimi Benzell, undated (Box 25)
  - 6 1/2x9 1/2 inch proof of Mimi Benzell, undated (Box 25)
  - 5 proofsheets of various poses by Mimi Benzell, undated (Box 25)
- Proposal: A PROPOSAL FOR STOMBERG-CARLSON, submitted by Shockley, Pokrass, and Gauss, Inc., 03/1950 (Box 25)
- Script - Opera: THE FORTUNE TELLER, liberetto by Harry B. Smith, music by Victor Herbert, typescript, 30 pages; carbon copy, 53 pages, lightly annotated, 1898: (Box 24)
- Scripts - Radio:
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "Peter Piper", Program No. 14, 3 pages, ditto, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "Eileen", Program No. 14, 7 pages, 2 ditto copies, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "Bitter Sweet", Program No. 13, 6 pages, 2 ditto copies, 1 ditto copy, 7 pages, lightly annotated, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "Sunny", Program No. 12, 5 pages, 3 ditto copies, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "No, No Nanette", Program No. 11, 6 pages, 2 ditto copies, 1 ditto copy, 9 pages, lightly annotated, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "The Chocolate Soldier", Program No. 10, 5 pages, 2 ditto copies, lightly annotated, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "Brigadoon", Program No. 9, 8 pages, 2 ditto copies, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "Rose Marie", Program No. 8, 5 pages, ditto: 6 pages, 2 ditto copies, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "One Touch of Venus", Program No. 7, 6 pages, 2 ditto copies, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "A Connecticut Yankee", Program No. 6, 4 pages, typescript; 1 ditto copy, 7 pages (2 page threes); 1 ditto copy, 6 pages, lightly annotated, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "The Student Prince", Program No. 5, 10 pages, 2 ditto copies, 6 pages, typescript, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "Naughty Marietta", Program No. 4, 6 pages, 5 ditto copies (one with 1 page insert), undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "Roberta", Program No. 3, 6 pages, 4 ditto copies; 1 ditto copy, 5 pages (page 4 missing), lightly annotated, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "The Vagabond King", Program No. 2, 7 pages, 3 ditto copies, lightly annotated, undated (Box 24)
  - Brayer, Judith, MUSICAL THEATRE, "H.M.S. Pinafore", Program No. 1, 6 pages, 3 ditto copies, lightly annotated, undated (Box 24)
  - Clarke, William Kendall, MGM MUSICAL COMEDY THEATRE, "It Happened in Brooklyn", 39 pages, mimeograph; second copy is 40 pages, undated (Box 24)
  - Holloway, Jean, RAILROAD HOUR, "The Desert Song", 23 pages, mimeograph, lightly annotated, 01/21/1952 (Box 24)
  - Lawrence and Lee, RAILROAD HOUR, "The Vagabond King", 18 pages, mimeograph, 11/24/1952 (Box 24)
  - Lawrence and Lee, RAILROAD HOUR, "The Gypsy Baron", 23 pages, mimeograph, lightly annotated, 01/21/1952 (Box 24)
  - Lawrence and Lee, RAILROAD HOUR, "East Wind" 19 pages, mimeograph, lightly annotated, 02/04/1952 (Box 24)
  - Lawrence and Lee, RAILROAD HOUR, "Sweethearts", 21 pages, mimeograph, 10/22/1951 (Box 24)
  - No Authors, BETTER VISION INSTITUTE-WONDERLAND OF VISION, Program No. 57, 7 page, mimeograph, undated (Box 24)
  - No Authors, BETTER VISION INSTITUTE-WONDERLAND OF VISION, Program No. 58, 7 pages, mimeograph, undated (Box 24)
  - No Authors, BETTER VISION INSTITUTE-WONDERLAND OF VISION, Program No. 59, 7 pages, mimeograph, undated (Box 24)
  - No Authors, THE EDGAR BERGEN-CHARLIE McCARTHY SHOW, 23 pages, mimeograph, 05/28/1950 (Box 24)
  - No Authors, EDGAR BERGEN WITH CHARLIE McCARTHY, Show #12, 21 pages, mimeograph, 12/21/1952 (Box 24)
  - No Authors, THE NORTHERNERS, Program No. 1056, 14 pages, mimeograph, 01/15/1952 (Box 24)
  - No Authors, RAILROAD HOUR, "Nina Rosa", 15 pages, mimeograph, 05/14/1951 (Box 24)
  - No Authors, THE WOOLWORTH HOUR, 26 pages, mimeograph, 08/05/1956 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 1, 21 pages, mimeograph, lightly annotated, 06/19/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 3, 22 pages, mimeograph, heavily annotated, 07/03/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 4, 24 pages, mimeograph, lightly annotated, 07/10/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 5, 21 pages, mimeograph, lightly annotated, 07/17/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 6, 21 pages, mimeograph, lightly annotated, 07/24/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 7, 23 pages, mimeograph, 07/31/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 8, 21 pages, mimeograph, lightly annotated, 08/07/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 9, 21 pages, mimeograph, heavily annotated, 08/14/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 10, 22 pages, mimeograph, lightly annotated, 08/21/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 11, 23 pages, mimeograph, lightly annotated, 08/28/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 12, 21 pages, mimeograph heavily annotated, 09/04/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 13, 21 pages, mimeograph, heavily annotated, 09/11/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 14, 22 pages, mimeograph, heavily annotated, 09/18/1951 (Box 24)
  - Wells, Billy K., THE PET MILK SHOW, Continuity No. 15, 21 pages, mimeograph, heavily annotated, 09/25/1951 (Box 24)
  - No Author, STARTIME, 19 pages, mimeograph, 02/23/1951 (Box 24)
- Scripts - Television:
  - Curran, Vincent, OFF THE RECORD, 15 pages, mimeograph, attachment, 10/05/1948 (Box 23)
  - Davenport, Marcia, LUCKYSTRIKE THEATRE, "Of Lena Geyer", mimeograph, 79 pages, with individual copies of Act I (26 pages) Act II (18 pages), and Act III (13 pages), annotated, 06/02/1952 (Box 23)
  - Lewis, Lester, HOLLYWOOD SCREEN TEST, 39 pages, mimeograph, 06/20/1948 (Box 23)
  - Markes, Larry and Jacobsen, Bill, CELEBRITIY TIME, 36 pages, mimeograph, 04/23/1950 (Box 23)
  - No Author, THE ALL STAR REVUE, 79 pages, mimeograph, with a rehearsal schedule and music for Pet Milk commercial, 11/22/1952 (Box 23)
  - No Author, AT HOME SHOW, Program #37, 10 pages, mimeograph, 05/21/1951 (Box 23)
  - No Author, THE CHOCOLATE SOLDIER, 77 pages, mimeograph, attachment, 10/30/1950 (Box 23)
  - No Author, COKETIME, Program #110, 17 pages, mimeograph, 05/14/1954 (Box 23)
  - No Author, GOODYEAR-PAUL WHITEMAN REVUE, 34 pages, mimeograph, 04/30/1950 (Box 23)
  - No Author, ON THE TOWN, 7 pages, mimeograph, 05/19/1956 (Box 23)
  - No Author, PAPST BLUE RIBBON CHRISTMAS SHOW 1953, 43 pages, mimeograph, 12/23/1953 (Box 23)
  - No Author, THE PAUL WINCHELL SHOW, 58 pages, mimeograph, lightly annotated, attachment, 03/28/1954 (Box 23)
  - No Author, STAR OF THE FAMILY, 20 pages, mimeograph, 07/29/1951 (Box 23)
  - No Author, TEXACO COMMAND APPEARANCE HONORING ED WYNN, 102 pages, mimeograph, 09/19/1957 (Box 23)
  - No Author, TEXACO STAR THEATER, Show #31, 57 pages, mimeograph, 04/15/1952 (Box 23)
- Scripts - Miscellaneous: